yottaa.com 2013-05-16

# Privacy Policy

_Last Updated 4/18/2011_

At Yottaa, Inc., we protect your privacy as if it were our own. We use the information you provide to us for several reasons including: to process your order(s), to reply to your questions, provide our newsletter via email, to provide our services, to facilitate a transaction you chose to enter into with our third party partner(s) and to incorporate your feedback into improvements to our Web site. We will not give, sell, or rent your personal information, including email address, or specific account activity to anyone for any reason without your prior consent except as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

This Statement of Privacy applies to the Yottaa website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Yottaa website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

  * ### Collection of your Personal Information

Yottaa collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home and/or work address and/or telephone number. Yottaa also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Yottaa. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Yottaa for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Yottaa website. Yottaa has implemented the services of Google Analytics and Kissmetrics.com and other similar services to implement first-party cookies to track visitor interactions.

Yottaa.com uses tracking technologies to send anonymous information about your browsing habits to a third party company. Links in our email communications to recipients are tracked via Web Beacons once you land on our website. Web Beacons appear on our website as 1x1 transparent images which transmit information such as your operating system, browser, resolution, geographical location, products ordered, and order total. This information is used to help our webmasters and marketers understand the behavior of visitors to our website and understand the effectiveness of online and email messages. Your information is submitted anonymously, and no sensitive or personally identifiable information is transmitted.

In the event that you contact us for customer support through the website, we may also request that you provide additional User Information relevant to the support requested by you. Users are under no obligation to provide such information. However, we cannot guarantee that we can provide customer support in the event that relevant information related to the use of our products or services is withheld. We may retain communications relating to customer support, and/or information drawn from such communications, for statistical and/or reference purposes.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Yottaa public message boards or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Yottaa does not read your private online communications with others.

  * ### Links

This site contains links to other sites. Yottaa is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Yottaa encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Yottaa so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Yottaa is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Yottaa and Yottaa family of websites or the use of your information by such outside websites.

  * ### Use of Your Personal Information

Yottaa collects and uses your personal information to operate the Yottaa website and deliver the services you have requested. Yottaa may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Yottaa and its affiliates. Yottaa may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.

Yottaa does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Yottaa may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Yottaa may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Yottaa, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Yottaa keeps track of the websites and pages you visit within the Yottaa service, in order to determine what Yottaa services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content within Yottaa to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Yottaa websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Yottaa or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Yottaa (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Yottaa, or the public.

  * ### Use of Cookies

The Yottaa website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Yottaa pages, or register with Yottaa site or services, a cookie helps Yottaa to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Yottaa website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Yottaa features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Yottaa services or websites you visit.

If you provide Yottaa with user information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:

    1. To review the user information that you have supplied to us
    2. To request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to us
    3. To request that your user information not be used to contact you
    4. To request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we use
    5. To request that your user information be deleted from our records and
    6. To opt out of being solicited by this website or third parties

If you request that your user information be deleted from our records, there may be a brief delay in our processing that request, while verify that the request is valid and originates from you as opposed to an unauthorized third party. If you request that your information be deleted, we reserve the right to terminate and/or limit your access to the Yottaa website.

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at info@Yottaa.com.

  * ### Security of your Personal Information

No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. Yottaa uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Yottaa secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

  * ### Changes to this Statement

Yottaa will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Yottaa encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Yottaa is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the "Last Updated" date above.

  * ### Enforcement of this Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact us at info@Yottaa.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or we have not addressed your inquiry to your satisfaction, you should then contact us at abuse@Yottaa.com.

  * ### To Unsubscribe From Yottaa

You may unsubscribe from Yottaa marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of the company’s emails or in the account and contact settings section of the Yottaa service.

  * ### Contact Information

Yottaa welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Yottaa has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Yottaa at info@Yottaa.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. Yottaa is located at:

Yottaa, Inc.   
101 Summer St, Boston   
MA 02110
